Guide to the Livingston Farrand papers, 1921-1939.
Farrand, Livingston Papers
- KEN-KENN Miscellaneous., 1933-35 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  Kendrick, M. Slade. Kenney Scholarships.
- KENN-Kent Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  Kenney Scholarships; the Cornell Rug.
- Kent-KEPP Miscellaneous., 1924-36 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  Frank, Waldo; Keppel, Frederick P. Harlan County, Kentucky; Carnegie Corporation.
- KEPP Miscellaneous., 1924-34 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  Keppel, Frederick P.; Fox, Dixon Ryan. Carnegie Corporation.
- Kerr, Abram T., 1923-37 (Box 17, Folder 23-29)
  Sumner, James T. Cornell University Medical College.
- Kerr-KET Miscellaneous., 1926-36 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  Kerr, W. J.
- KET-KIL Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  Ketchum, Milo S.; Keynes, John Maynard.
- Kimball, Dexter S., 1922-37 (Box 17, Folder 32-47)
- KIMB-King Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 17, Folder 48)
- King-Kingsbury Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  Kingsbury, B. F.
- Kingsbury-Kingsley Miscellaneous., 1921-32 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  Kingsbury, B. F.; Adelmann, Howard B. Cornell University Medical College.
- Kinkeldey, Otto., 1923-37 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  University Library.
- Kinkeldey, Otto., 1923-34 (Box 18, Folder 1-4)
- Kinley-KIRK Miscellaneous., 1924-37 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  Kinley, David. University of Illinois.
- KIRK-Klotz Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  Kleinfeld, Philip L. National Child Labor Committee; Brooklyn Jewish Democracy, Inc.
- Klotz-Knopf Miscellaneous., 1925-29 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Knickerbacker, John., 1922-35 (Box 18, Folder 8-11)
- Knight-Knopf Miscellaneous., 1926-36 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  Knopf, S. Adolphus.
- Knopf-Knudson Miscellaneous., 1923-30 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  Knopf, S. Adolphus; Knudson, Lewis. Knox College.
- Knudson-Kopald Miscellaneous., 1921-33 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  Koffka, Kurt; Kolbe, Parke R.
- Kopald-Kotlan Miscellaneous., 1922-32 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  Korn, C. F.
- KR-Kruse Miscellaneous., 1924-33 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  Krishna, Rama; Kruse, Otto V.
- Kruse, Paul J., 1919-32 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Krusen-Kupalov Miscellaneous., 1926-34 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  Kunic, Miso; Kupalov, P.
- Kupalov-Kwouk Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  Kupalov, P.; Gregg, Alan.
- KR-KU Miscellaneous., 1935-37 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  Dewey, John; Kraus, Arthur J.; Kulp, Claude L.
- Ladd, Carl E., 1924-37 (Box 18, Folder 21-25)
- LA-LAI Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  Lafayette College; Labor; United States Dept. of Labor.
- LAI Miscellaneous., 1924-34 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  Laistner, M. L. W.
- LAI-LAK Miscellaneous. Laistner, M. L. W. Lake Forest Academy., 1925-33 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- LAK-LAM Miscellaneous., 1926-36 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  Lam, George L. Lake Placid Club Education Foundation.
- LAM-LAN Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  Lamont, Thomas W.; Lancaster, Bruce. Association of Land-Grant Colleges and Universities.
- LAND Miscellaneous., 1921-37 (Box 18, Folder 31-32)
  Clarke, Gilmour D. Dept. of Landscape Architecture. Land grant colleges.
- Lane-LANG Miscellaneous., 1926-30 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  Langdon, Jervis.
- LANG-LAT Miscellaneous., 1921-26 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  Langdon, Jervis; Lapie, Paul.
- LATT-LAU Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  Lattimore, Owen; de Coubertin, Pierre. Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial.
- LAV-LAW Miscellaneous. Van Cleef, Mynderse; Palmer, Archie M. Law School., 1922-34 (Box 18, Folder 36)
- LAW Miscellaneous., 1931-35 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  Lawrenceville School.
- Lawrenceville School., 1929-35 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  Noyes, Jansen.
- LAW-LAZ Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  Lawson, Edward. Law School.
- LE-LEA Miscellaneous., 1924-35 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  League of Nations.
- LEAG-LEAH Miscellaneous., 1923-31 (Box 18, Folder 41)
- Lear-Lee Miscellaneous., 1922-25 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  Smith, Goldwin.
- Lee-LEF Miscellaneous., 1921-27 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  Lee, Ivy L.
- LEF-LEH Miscellaneous., 1922-31 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  Lehigh University; Lehigh Valley Railroad Company.
- LEH Miscellaneous., 1921-37 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  Lehman, Herbert H.; Griffis, Stanton. Lehigh Valley Railroad Company; Cornell University Board of Trustees.
- LEH-LEI Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  Leighton, Alexander H.
- LEI-LEO Miscellaneous., 1925-35 (Box 18, Folder 47)
- LEO-LETT Miscellaneous., 1922-27 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  LePaulle, Pierre; Lester, O. C.
- LETT-LEW Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  Levine, Samuel; Lewin, Kurt.
- LEW-LEY Miscellaneous., 1921-35 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  Lewis, William Mather.
- LI-LIB Miscellaneous., 1930-37 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  White, J. DuPratt. Cornell University Library.
- Cornell University Library., 1928-36 (Box 18, Folder 52-53)
- LIC-LID Miscellaneous., 1935-37 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  Liddell, Howard S.
- Liddell Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 18, Folder 55-56)
  Liddell, Mark H.; Liddell, Howard S.
- LEI-LIM Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  Lilly Fellowship; Eli Lilly and Company.
- LIM-LIN Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  Lincoln, Paul Martyn. School of Electrical Engineering.
- LIN Miscellaneous., 1924-36 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  Lincoln, Paul Martyn; Taft, William H. Lincoln Memorial; Lincoln University.
- LIN-LIT Miscellaneous., 1928-37 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  Lippmann, Walter; Lit, D. E. (Mrs. ).
- LIT-LIV Miscellaneous., 1921-33 (Box 18, Folder 61)
- LL Miscellaneous., 1928-36 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  Cheeseman, Charles; Mann, Albert R. Lloyd Library and Museum.
- LOC-LOE Miscellaneous., 1926-29 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  Lochoff, Nicolas.
- Loewy, Benno., 1919 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Loewy-Long Miscellaneous., 1919-34 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  Loewy, Benno.
- Long-LOT Miscellaneous., 1924-36 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  Lorentz, H. A. Loomis Institute.
- University of Louvain., 1922-23 (Box 19, Folder 6-8)
  Pringle, W. Gordon; Butler, Nicholas Murray.
- Love, H. H., 1925-37 (Box 19, Folder 9-10)
  University of Nanking; China.
- LOV-Lunn Miscellaneous., 1922-32 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  Lovell, Earl B.; Lowrie, Charles N.; Lund, Wallace; Lunn, Henry. Committee on Buildings and Grounds; Anglo-American Committee for International Discussion.
- Lunn-Lyons Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  Lunn, Henry; Lynah, James.
- Lynah, James. Dept. of Physical Education; Ivy League., 1935-37 (Box 19, Folder 13-14)
- McA Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  McAlpin, Charles W.
- McA-McC Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  McBride, George M.
- McC Miscellaneous., 1922-32 (Box 19, Folder 17-18)
  McConnell, Francis J.
- McC-McD Miscellaneous., 1922-28 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  MacCracken, Henry N.; MacDaniels, Laurence H.
- McD-McF Miscellaneous., 1921-28 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  MacDonald, William; McFadden, Thomas J.; Me Fadden, Harrison D.
- McG Miscellaneous., 1921-33 (Box 19, Folder 21-23)
  McGill University; McGovern, John T.
- McG-McI Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  McGovern, John T.; McHarg, Henry K.
- McI-McK Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- McK Miscellaneous., 1923-34 (Box 19, Folder 26-27)
  Mackay, Melba; McKenna, James Augustine.
- NcNullen Scholarships., 1932-37 (Box 19, Folder 28-29)
- McL-McM Miscellaneous., 1923-30 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  McMaster University.
- McM Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 19, Folder 31-32)
  Macmillan, Kerr D. Wells College.
- McMullen Undergraduate Scholars., 1929-30 (Box 19, Folder 33)
- McM Miscellaneous., 1926-29 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  Kimball, Dexter S.
- McM-McN Miscellaneous., 1921-30 (Box 19, Folder 35)
- McN-McV Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 19, Folder 36)
- McV Miscellaneous., 1925-30 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  McWhood, Leonard B.
- MAD-MAJ Miscellaneous., 1922-26 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  Madison, John; Maidl, Francis. University of Maine.
- MAJ-MAL Miscellaneous., 1928-33 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  Malinowski, Bronislaw.
- MAL-MAN Miscellaneous., 1927-34 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  Manch, Daniel; Mandel, Leon; Mangan, Thomas J.
- MAN-Mann Miscellaneous., 1927-34 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  Verbeck, Guido F.
- Mann-MANU Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  Mann, Paul B.
- Mann, Albert R., 1922-25 (Box 19, Folder 43-59)
- Mann, Albert R., 1925-28 (Box 20, Folder 1-17)
- Mann, Albert R., Surveys., 1929 (Box 20, Folder 18-25)
- Mann, Albert R., 1930-31 (Box 20, Folder 26-37)
- MAP-MAR Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  Mano, Bunji; Marcham, Frederick G.
- MAR Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 20, Folder 39-42)
  Martin, Clarence A. Marietta College; Mark Twain Centennial Committee.
- MAS -Mason Miscellaneous., 1928-30 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  Masaryk, Thomas G.; Borglum, Gutzon; Norton, Elliott S.; Dobie, Gilmour.
- Mason Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 20, Folder 44-45)
  Mason, Herbert D.; Dobie, Gilmour; Mason, James F.; Mason, Max. University of Oklahoma.
- Massachusetts Miscellaneous., 1920-32 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  University of Massachusetts; Massachusetts Institute of Technology.
- Mass-MAST Miscellaneous., 1924-36 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  Massey, L. M.
- MAST-MATH Miscellaneous., 1921-30 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  Mather, Frank Jewett; Mather, Stephen T.
- MATHE Miscellaneous. Matheson, Robert., 1928-32 (Box 20, Folder 49)
- Matthews Miscellaneous., 1922-32 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  Mathews, Shailer.
- MATT-MAX Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  Maury, Carlotta J.; Ries, H. Caribbean Petroleum Co.; Paleontological Laboratory.
- MAX-MAY Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  Mayer, Joseph; Maynard, L. A.
- Mayer Miscellaneous., 1923-34 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  Bergholtz, Herman.
- MEA-MED Miscellaneous., 1924-36 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  Meara, Frank S.; Medary, M. B.
- Cornell University Medical College. Andresen, Jessie P., 1923-33 (Box 21, Folder 1-10)
- Cornell University Medical College A-C., 1929-36 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  Barry, Margaret; Cecil, Russell L.
- Cornell University Medical College C-D., 1926-37 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  Crawford, Mary M. Medical College Alumni Association.
- Cornell University Medical College D., 1924-35 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  Dana, Charles L.; Du Bois, Eugene F.
- Cornell University Medical College D-E., 1930-35 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  Elser, William J. Society of the New York Hospital.
- Cornell University Medical College E., 1928-30 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Cornell University Medical College F., 1924-35 (Box 21, Folder 16-19)
  Ferguson, J. S.; Fox, Barry.
- Cornell University Medical College G., 1921-35 (Box 21, Folder 20-22)
  Gibson, Charles L.
- Cornell University Medical College G-H., 1923-34 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  Hartwell, John A.
- Cornell University Medical College H., 1922-35 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  Hinsey, Joseph C.
- Cornell University Medical College H-L., 1934-35 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  Kennedy, Foster.
- Cornell University Medical College L., 1927-33 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  Lusk, Graham.
- Cornell University Medical College -Ladd, William S., 1932-37 (Box 21, Folder 27-35)
- Cornell University Medical College -Niles, Walter L., 1921-28 (Box 21, Folder 36-50)
- Cornell University Medical College -Niles, Walter L., 1928-30 (Box 22, Folder 1-6)
- Cornell University Medical College Miscellaneous., 1928-37 (Box 22, Folder 7-11)
- Cornell University Medical College-Robinson, G. Canby., 1928-33 (Box 22, Folder 12-47)
- Cornell University Medical College O-S., 1930-36 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  Russell, William L.
- Cornell University Medical College S., 1934-37 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  Smillie, Wilson G.
- Cornell University Medical College S-T., 1925-34 (Box 22, Folder 50-51)
  Stockard, C. R.
- Cornell University Medical College., 1921-32 (Box 22, Folder 52-57)
  Willson, J. Thorn.
- Cornell University Medical College., 1924 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Medicine-Medina., 1923-27 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  Moore, H. H.
- Meeks-MEL Miscellaneous., 1931-37 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  Meeks, Everett V.
- MEL-MELL Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  Melchers, Gari; Butler, Nicholas Murray.
- MELL-MELO Miscellaneous., 1924-35 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  Albee, Edward F.; Curie, Marie; Meloney, Marie M.; Melvin, Bruce L. Mellon Tax Reduction Proposal.
- Meek, Howard B., 1929-34 (Box 23, Folder 6-10)
  Hotel School; Hotel Ezra Cornell.
- Memorial Hospital., 1926-35 (Box 23, Folder 11-12)
  Merriam, Norton H.
- Memorial Hospital-MEN Miscellaneous., 1931-34 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- MEN-MERR Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  Mennen, William G.
- MERR Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  Merrill, Harold; Young, George; Merrill, Theodore C.
- Merritt, Ernest., 1921-34 (Box 23, Folder 16-20)
  Dept. of Physics.
- Messenger Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  Messenger Lectures.
- Messenger-MET Miscellaneous., 1926-36 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  Metcalf, William; Coryllos, Polyvius; Metropulos, P.
- MET-MEX Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- MEX-MEZ Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  Mexico; University of Mexico.
- MI-MIDD Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- MIDD-MIL Miscellaneous., 1924-37 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  Middle States Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools.
- MIL-MILL Miscellaneous., 1923-31 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- MILL-Miller Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  Miller, Frank H.; Miller, James Alexander.
- Miller-Mills Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  Miller, Kelly.
- Mills-MILW Miscellaneous., 1930-36 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  Mills, Nelson.
- Milwaukee., 1922-26 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- MIM-MINNS Miscellaneous., 1921-36 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  Harrington, Charles M. Miner Foundation.
- MINNS-MISS Miscellaneous., 1924-35 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  Minns, Lua A.
- MISS-NIT Miscellaneous., 1927-35 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  Mitchell, James McC.
- MIT-MIY Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  Mitchell, James McC.; Mitchell, Wesley C.
- MIY-MOB Miscellaneous., 1924-34 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  Betzinger, Helen Holt. Milbank Memorial Fund; Mobilization for Human Needs (1934).
- MOB-MOD Miscellaneous., 1931-36 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  Modak, D. S. Mobilization for Human Needs.
- MOD-MOE Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  League of Nations Model Assembly.
- MOD-MOL Miscellaneous., 1926-34 (Box 23, Folder 39)
- MOL-MON Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  Monroe, B. S.
- MON-MONT Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  Monsch, Helen.
- MONT-Moore Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  Moody, Harriet T.
- Moore Miscellaneous., 1920-35 (Box 23, Folder 43-44)
  Moore, Clyde B.; Moore, John B.; Moore, Norman S. United Christian Work at Cornell.
- Moore, Veranus A., 1921-30 (Box 23, Folder 45-50)
  New York State Veterinary College.
- MORA Miscellaneous., 1921-35 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  Moran, Hugh A. Foundation for Moral and Religious Leadership.
- Moran, Hugh A., 1925-35 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  United Christian Work at Cornell.
- Moran-MORD Miscellaneous., 1923-28 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  Moran, Hugh A. University of Nanking.
- MORD-Morgan Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 23, Folder 54)
- Morgan-Moro Miscellaneous., 1925-35 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  Morgan, Thomas Hunt; Morgenthau, Henry; Morley, Sylvanus G.
- Moro Educational Foundation., 1924-35 (Box 23, Folder 56-58)
  Roosevelt, Theodore; Mar, Curtis J.
- MORR Miscellaneous., 1922-31 (Box 23, Folder 59)
  Morrison, Frank B.
- MORR-MORS Miscellaneous., 1931-35 (Box 23, Folder 60)
  Morsbach, Adolf.
- MORS Miscellaneous., 1924-34 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- MORT-Motor Miscellaneous., 1922-31 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  Motion Picture Research Council.
- Motor-Mott Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  Mott, John R. Parking.
- Mott, John R., 1928-34 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Mott-MOTW Miscellaneous., 1921-34 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Mount Miscellaneous., 1924-36 (Box 24, Folder 6-7)
  Mountford, James Frederick; Caplan, Harry; Woolley, Mary E. Mount Holyoke College.
- Mount-MUN Miscellaneous., 1928-37 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  Mulliken, Alfred.
- MUN-MUR Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  Mundy, Floyd W.; Munson, David C.; Murdock, Carleton C. Dept. of Physics.
- MUR-MUS Miscellaneous., 1923-34 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  Hennings, Thomas C.
- MUS-MY Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  Myers, C. H. University of Nanking.
- NY Miscellaneous., 1930-31 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  Myron Taylor Hall.
- Music Miscellaneous., 1920-28 (Box 24, Folder 13-14)
  Whittaker, W. G.; Thilly, Frank; Kinkeldey, Otto; Adler, Lawrence; Morrey, Marion. Dept. of Music.
- NAF-NAN Miscellaneous. Love, H. H.; Chen, Y. G. University of Nanking; China Union Universities., 1922-32 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- NAN-NAS Miscellaneous., 1922-31 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  Chen, Y. G.; Nash, A. Douglas. University of Nanking.
- NAS-NAT Miscellaneous., 1923-30 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  Nash, A. Douglas.
- National A., 1922-37 (Box 24, Folder 18-19)
  Hoover, Herbert; Mann, Albert R. National Academy of Sciences; National Association of State Universities.
- National A-B., 1918-34 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  National Association of State Universities.
- National B-C., 1923-36 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  National Broadcasting Company.
- National C., 1922-36 (Box 24, Folder 22-26)
  National Child Labor Committee; National Collegiate Athletic Association; National Committee for Mental Hygiene; National Conference on College Hygiene; National Conference of Christians and Jews.
- National C-E., 1921-33 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  National Economic League.
- National E., 1922-34 (Box 24, Folder 28-29)
  Moore, Harry H. National Education Association.
- National Council for the Advancement Of Secondary Education., 1933-36 (Box 24, Folder 30-36)
  Moore, Harry H.
- National Council on Religion in Higher Education., 1927-36 (Box 24, Folder 37-40)
- National F-I., 1929-37 (Box 24, Folder 41)
- National I., 1924-36 (Box 24, Folder 42-43)
  National Industrial Conference Board.
- National I-R., 1926-34 (Box 24, Folder 44)
- National R., 1921-35 (Box 24, Folder 45-49)
  National Recovery Administration; National Research Council.
- National S - NAT Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 24, Folder 50-51)
  National Student Federation; Naturalization.
- NAV-NEB Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 24, Folder 52)
- NEB-NEED Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  Needham, James G.
- NEED-NEET Miscellaneous., 1926-34 (Box 24, Folder 54)
- NEF-NEL Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 24, Folder 55)
- NEL-NEU Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 24, Folder 56)
- NEU-NEW Miscellaneous., 1924-27 (Box 24, Folder 57)
  Nevins, Allan.
- NEW-NEWB Miscellaneous., 1926-35 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  Farrand, Wilson. Newark, N. J.
- NEWB-NEW E Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  Newell, F. H. New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools.
- NEW E-NEW H Miscellaneous., 1927-36 (Box 24, Folder 60)
- NEW H-NEW J Miscellaneous., 1924-35 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  Terriberry, G. Gilson.
- NEW J Miscellaneous., 1931-33 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  League for a Free State University in New Jersey.
- NEWK-NEWM Miscellaneous. Newman, Jared T., 1922-32 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- NEWM-NEW T Miscellaneous., 1929-37 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  Newman, Jared T.; Fleming, Bryant.
- New York Academy of Medicine., 1929-37 (Box 25, Folder 5-7)
- N. Y. A-C Miscellaneous., 1925-35 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- N. Y. C-H Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  LeBoeuf, Randall J.; Gavit, John P.
- New York Hospital., 1927-37 (Box 25, Folder 10-33)
  Sheldon, Edward W.; Flexner, Abraham; Powell, Wilson M.; Wolf, Anna D.;: Lancaster, Bruce. Cornell University Medical College; Society of the New York Hospital; New York Hospital School of Nursing; New York Hospital-Cornell Medical College Association Joint Administrative Board.
- New York Hospital Final Agreement., 1927 (Box 25, Folder 34-37)
- New York Hospital., 1933 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  General Education Board; Medical Board.
- N. Y. I-S Miscellaneous., 1923-33 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- N. Y. S. A-C Miscellaneous., 1921-37 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  New York State Agricultural Society.
- N. Y. S. C-F Miscellaneous., 1927-32 (Box 25, Folder 41)
- N. Y. S. F Miscellaneous., 1927-34 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  New York State Farm Bureau Federation.
- N. Y. S. G-M Miscellaneous., 1923-33 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  New York State League of Women Voters.
- N. Y. S. M-T Miscellaneous., 1924-34 (Box 25, Folder 44)
- N. Y. S. T-W Miscellaneous., 1922-30 (Box 25, Folder 45)
- N. Y. S-T Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  New York Stock Exchange.
- New York Times., 1922-35 (Box 25, Folder 47)
- N. Y. U-W Miscellaneous., 1927-37 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  New York University.
- N. Y. W-NI Miscellaneous., 1922-29 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  White, J. DuPratt. New York World's Fair.
- Nicholls, James Z., 1926-37 (Box 25, Folder 50-55)
  Military Dept.
- NIC-NIE Miscellaneous., 1923-33 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  Nichols, Edward L.; Nichols, M. L.
- NIE-NO Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  Niebuhr, Reinhold.
- Nobel-NOG Miscellaneous., 1928-36 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  Van de Mark, R. W.; Nolan, J. Bennett.
- NOL-NOR Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  Nolan, J. Bennett; Norlin, George. University of Colorado; University of Heidelberg.
- NOR-NORR Miscellaneous., 1924-30 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  Norlin, George.
- North Miscellaneous., 1927-33 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  Graham, Frank P. University of North Carolina.
- North-Northern Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  Chase, H. W. University of North Carolina.
- Northern-Northrup Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  Northrup, Clark S.
- Northrup-Norton Miscellaneous., 1922-30 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Norton Miscellaneous., 1923-29 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  Fraternities.
- Norton-NOT Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  Norton, Paul L.; Antell, Bert; Norton, W. J.
- NOT-Noyes Miscellaneous., 1921-34 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  Notestein, Wallace; Noyes, Jansen.
- Noyes Miscellaneous., 1925-37 (Box 26, Folder 13-14)
  Noyes, Nicholas H. University of Chicago.
- NU-Nye Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Nye-OB Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  Nye, Gertrude.
- OB-OD Miscellaneous., 1929-32 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  Oberlin College.
- OD-OG Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Ogden, R. M., 1921-36 (Box 26, Folder 19-44)
  College of Arts and Sciences.
- Ogden-Ohio., 1922-32 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  Ogden, Warren G. Ohio State University.
- Ohio-OLD Miscellaneous., 1921-37 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  University of Oklahoma.
- Oldham, G. Ashton., 1932-37 (Box 26, Folder 47)
- Oldham-Olin Miscellaneous. Oldham, G. Ashton; O'Leary, Paul M.; Olin, Franklin W., 1923-37 (Box 26, Folder 48)
- Olin-Oliver Miscellaneous., 1928-37 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  Olin, Franklin W.
- OLM-OLY Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 26, Folder 50)
- OLY-OM Miscellaneous., 1931-36 (Box 26, Folder 51)
- ON-OP Miscellaneous., 1923-34 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  O'Neill, James.
- OP-OPP Miscellaneous., 1926-30 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  Open Road, Inc.
- OPP-OR Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  Oppenheimer, Robert.
- OR-ORR Miscellaneous., 1920-32 (Box 26, Folder 55)
- ORR-OSB Miscellaneous., 1925-36 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  Orton, Lawrence M.; Orton, Jesse F.; Doubleday, Nelson.
- OSB-OSM Miscellaneous., 1926-36 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  Osborn, Henry Fairfield. American Museum of Natural History.
- OSM-OUZ Miscellaneous., 1921-30 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  Ostrom, John N.
- OV-OX Miscellaneous., 1924-32 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  Owsley, Mike.
- PAC-Pack Miscellaneous., 1927-34 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  Pack, Arthur Newton.
- Pack Miscellaneous., 1926-28 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  Fred, Erwin P.; Pack, Arthur Newton; Pack, Charles Lathrop.
- Pack-PAD Miscellaneous., 1921-27 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  Pack, Arthur Newton; Snyder, Virgil. American Tree Association; Kosciuszko Foundation.
- Page-PAL Miscellaneous., 1924-37 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  Paine, Ernest T.; Palmer, Archie M.
- Palmer, Archie M., 1923-37 (Box 27, Folder 9-12)
  Cornellian Council; Alumni Fund.
- Palmer Miscellaneous., 1923-33 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  Palmer, E. Laurence.
- Pan Am I-U Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  Pan American Union.